bfads.net 2018-05-26

# Black Friday Ads - Legal Information and Privacy Policy

Effective Date: February 8, 2018

This Privacy Policy Statement applies to [www.bfads.net](http://www.bfads.net/) ("BFADs" or "BFADs.net") owned and operated by Ebates Inc. This Privacy Policy Statement describes how we collect, use, share, and secure your personal information and other shopping information. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of this information and how you can access and update this information. If you have a question about this Privacy Policy Statement, you can contact our Chief Privacy Officer by email at [privacy@ebates.com](mailto:privacy@ebates.com?subject=Privacy%20Inquiry%20Regarding%20Ebates.com).

## Information We Collect and How We Use It

Our vision is to maximize your rewards and to provide you with as many member benefits as possible. The key way in which we provide value is to share with you the commissions we receive from our merchant partners in the form of Cash Back. We strive to confirm and pay your Cash Back quickly and reliably, and to improve your experience on our site and in our applications Ð these are the main reasons we collect information.

## BFADs.net

When you become a member of BFADs.net, we collect your name, email address, and physical address ("Personal Information"). We use your Personal Information to track and to improve and personalize our services. We also collect information pertaining to our merchant partners you visit, the purchases you make, and the offers you view ("Transaction Information"). We use Transaction Information to provide more relevant offers for you when you visit us or use our applications and services.

## Social Media

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect your IP address and the page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. These social media features may be hosted by us or a third party. Your interactions with social media features hosted by third parties (such as the Facebook Like button) are governed by the privacy policies of the companies providing them.

## Third Party Log-In Services

We allow you to log in to BFADs and our mobile app using services such as Facebook, Google Plus, and Twitter. These services authenticate your identity and provides you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address in order to pre-populate our sign-up form. These services allow you to share information about your activities on BFADs with others in your network. We may integrate with, and make available to you, other third-party log-in services in the future.

## Email Account Connection

We allow you to connect your personal email account to your BFADs account in order to view your purchase confirmations on BFADs.net. We share this Transaction Information as needed with our affiliate network partners and merchant partners in order to provide you more relevant and interesting offers. You may choose to connect your email account to your BFADs account, or to disconnect it, by making a selection in the My Profile section of our site. A connection between your email account and your BFADs account is not required for you to be a member of BFADs.net.

## Who Sees Your Personal Information

We share your Personal Information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy Statement. We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. Only a very limited number of our employees ever have access to your Personal Information.

We may use contractors or vendors to help us provide some of the services on BFADs, some of whom may be our corporate affiliates (for instance, payment fulfillment or marketing services). If we need to disclose Personal Information for them to provide such services, it is with the requirement that such Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used only for those services.

We reserve the right to disclose information we collect (including Personal Information) as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or other lawful requests by public authorities, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us or our corporate affiliates, or to protect us, our corporate affiliates, or our members from losses.

## How We Keep Your Information Secure

The security of your Personal Information is important to BFADs. We use a secure, encrypted connection (called an SSL connection) on all pages where you access or transmit Personal Information. In addition, we encrypt your credit card information that you have given us to store, and maintain industry standard security to safeguard this information. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Your Privacy With BFADs

Ebates will never ask for your email address, username, password or any other Personal Information in an unsolicited phone call, email or letter. Further, any contact with BFADs customer service in which Personal Information is exchanged with a customer service representative will be used only for the purpose of satisfying your request. Any Personal Information you provide will not be recorded or used for any reason beyond that of the stated request.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

If we materially modify this Privacy Policy Statement, we will post a change notice in a prominent place on our site or by notifying you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account before the change becomes effective). We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy Statement at any time, so please review it regularly.

## Links to Third Party Websites

Ebates contains links to many other websites. Each of these websites should have its own Privacy Policy Statement that may differ materially from this Privacy Policy Statement. If you wish to receive special offers directly from a merchant partner, neither this Privacy Policy Statement nor our opt-out policy applies to those communications. Instead, please refer to the relevant merchant partner's privacy and opt-out policy.

## Our Policies on Email

BFADs sends two types of emails to members: customer service emails required to maintain the BFADs' programs and promotional emails containing offers. You may choose not to receive promotional emails at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in any promotional email or filling out the contact form found [here](https://www.bfads.net/Contact). 

## Cookies and Other Technologies

We, Ebates Inc., and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. 

## Other Information We Collect

As is true of most web sites, we gather and store certain information automatically. This information may include, but is not necessarily limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and adminster the site. We link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about users in order to improve our services and to guard against malicious activity.

## Behavioral Targeting

We use one or more vendors to manage our advertising on other sites. Our vendors may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Your Choices and Responsibilities

It is your responsibility to update and maintain accurate contact information in your BFADs account. You can make changes by visiting the My Profile page and entering corrections. Upon request, we will provide you with the information about whether we hold any of your personal information. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. The email and street address that you enter into your My Profile page is the information that will be used for all contact with you. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as long as you have a balance greater than zero in your account. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Please feel free to contact us at [ privacy@ebates.com](mailto:privacy@ebates.com?subject=Privacy%20Inquiry%20Regarding%20Ebates.com) if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy Statement or our privacy and personal information practices.

## Dispute Resolution

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

BFADs.net  
525 Third Street Suite C  
Beloit, WI 53511
